LEAH ANESTOS

JUNIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

From an early age and throughout her entire professional journey, she has consistently been acknowledged as the go-to person for troubleshooting critical challenges, ranging from computer issues to recognizing ineffective strategies in the workplace. Both current and previous colleagues & supervisors, have utilized her exceptional ability to address diverse technology-related challenges with precision and efficiency, establishing her as the trusted point person for resolving issues promptly. Motivated by these experiences, and a desire to learn and complete new challenges, she transitioned to Software Engineering in 2023 to further develop her technical skills and contribute to impactful projects.

PROJECTS



https://leahanestosportfolio.netlify.app



https://github.com/leahkatherine

EDUCATION

NuCamp

Full Stack Web Developer Mar 2023 - October 2023

QUALIFICATIONS

- 1.5 years of growing development experience
- Experienced Full Stack Technologies with React & React Native, JavaScript & TypeScript, Next js, Node js, Express, Docker, and familiarity with both MongoDB & PostgreSQL.
- Five years of proven leadership and management expertise, adeptly guiding teams to successfully achieve organizational objectives.
- Brings over a decade of experience in customer service, skilled in navigating conversations with professionalism and adept at finding common ground.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Full Stack Software Engineer

Danica's Custom Bakes Dec 2023 - Present

- Implements new features and tools to enhance client-side and admin-side user experience.
- Brings a sales and marketing perspective to web page design, enhancing creativity and user engagement.
- · React/Next.js for front-end, alongside Node.js/Prisma(ORM)/Docker for back-end development.

Part-Time Cashier & Wire Operator

Stifel Investments Nov 2023 - Present

- Deposits check transactions & manages office correspondence by way of email, letters, and phone calls.
- Offers troubleshooting support to all colleagues, resolving a wide array of technology-related issues and challenges they face.

Relief Sales Rep

Southern Eagle Distributing July 2020-August 2021

- Strategically resolved stock shortages, assisting team in achieving sales goals amidst industry challenges.
- Cultivated and repaired client relationships, ensuring satisfaction and fostering long-term partnerships.
- Collected product orders for a large jurisdiction of local restaurants

Full Stack Software Engineer Student

NuCamp Mar 2023 - Oct 2023

- Completed 5 four-week courses focused on rapid skill development in full-stack web and mobile development technologies.
- Transitioned from a hospitality career to dedicate full-time efforts to course assignments, projects, and learning JavaScript.

Cruise and Event Planning Manager

Savannah Riverboat Cruises Aug 2021 - June 2023

- · Managed cruise and event planning operations, overseeing a range of onboard events and experiences.
- · Lead project manager in updating sales tools, event menus, signage, and sales & marketing material.

Assistant Boat Manager

Savannah Riverboat Cruises

Feb 2016 - May 2019

- Collaborated with executives and chefs to optimize event operations for up to 1000 attendees.
- · Developed training materials and streamlined operations for serving, bartending, and POS systems.
- Gained proficiency in every position aboard, including legal qualifications for Coast Guard, Serv Safe, and Bar Card Certifications.